People!
Today is Sunday and it is officially time to open a coke.
I have gotten permission from my dentist.
We're back on coke!
I also have a I have a IPA beer in the fridge but it needs to cool down first so I'm waiting for that as well.
It needs to be ice cold before I consume that beverage.
Legalize coke!
It's already legal man and it's great.
It's so good.
Man, I have big plans today.
I say that every time I play Neuter but I'm actually so excited to to kill some dudes.
It's been a while man.
I've had that craving for the Neuter.
It's like an inexplicable craving you know.
Like you get your ass handed to you all the time.
It's like going to McDonald's.
You know you crave this classic cheeseburger, the coin offer, you eat it and you feel like shit afterwards.
Well not always but you know you get your ass kicked basically.
But the next day you crave it again.
It's like a weird relationship you have.
That's how I feel with this game.
It's so weird.
How long you think you're gonna stream for?
I don't know.
I want to stream quite a bit.
I want to I want to get a good chunk of time into Neuter today.
I can't say for certain but I don't know.
A decently long stream I would say.
Hey Narf, thank you for subscribing.
Thank you so much.
With the Prime as well.
And Codoplex!
Three months, love this man.
No I love you.
I love your name.
Codoplex.
I feel like that's a reference to something.
Is it?
I've seen that name before somewhere.
Codoplex.
Ah man it feels good.
It is a little too hot today though.
I would... I wish it was a little colder.
I'm dying inside of here man.
I have my window fully open.
Jump over here.
Remove that.
No technical issues at all.
Everything is smooth.
Hope you enjoy them off to bed.
Good night Josiah.
I guess I am streaming at a bit of a... well unusual time.
For me it's 1.30 in the afternoon.
So it's quite the perfect time to stream.
The place where I live at least.
My sleep is very brief.
Go back to sleep.
You don't have to watch this.
You gotta value your health first.
Unless you're actually fine to keep going.
Hmm.
Oh and I'm gonna enjoy.
Don't worry Josiah.
So Codoplex.
I don't know if that was a reference to anything.
I don't think Codoplex is here.
I was curious to get that confirmed or not.
Okay.
I am jumping in.
Apparently we're in the middle of a run.
I guess we technically are in the middle of a run.
But we didn't get very far.
I must have died.
Not a big surprise I guess.
Okay so the plan for today is I am once again gonna try to perform the sacred quest of getting high.
Three times.
And see if anything reveals itself.
So that means we're gonna need the demon eye.
And what do I have?
I have swamp.
That's cool.
Demon eye.
And also other things that are on my list here.
Let's just quickly remind ourselves.
We need to murder the ancient laboratory.
We did that already but I guess that's an ongoing thing.
We can always do that.
Because it's good to murder him.
The demon eye platforms.
We did do a bit of that.
I want to keep it on here though.
That one I'm still unsure why I wrote that but I'm gonna keep it here.
The music wand.
I think I just want to kind of try and brute force some combinations at some point.
Just to see what trouble I can get into.
The music box riddle.
I tried that.
Was it last time or the time before that?
And nothing happened.
At least the way I understood it of course.
Maybe I didn't get it right.
And that's very possible.
I gotta try some new things.
I'm gonna keep it on here for now because there's definitely something going on.
Right?
Try teleportation in eye and snowy depths.
That one is big.
I'm like 99% sure that's that's the correct thing to do.
This one is of course.
I think I did that a little bit but then I died.
Yeah.
For now that's good.
We have the map.
Everything's looking great.
I'm particularly fond of my drawing here.
The little zoom in.
It's cool, huh?
Also hold on a second.
I need to make sure this is working correctly.
There we go.
Okay.
Don't make a circle there.
You dummy.
All right.
I think it's time.
And we have the music cue going on so that I cannot forget to change the scene.
You guys shall never be cursed with the map overlay while I play ever again.
A mysterious darkness lingers here now.
That's fine with me.
So one of the first things we got to do is go grab the tablet.
Because that's one way to deal with the steward man.
The steward man himself.
Big S.
One of the gods' peoples who do tasks for the... I don't know what the... steward, right?
Actual steward.
Steward of the holy temple.
Also I do not like that there's a mysterious darkness here because then I can't tell where I've been.
That's okay though.
I shall try to remember anyway.
Mm-hmm.
What's that?
Green slimy meat.
Okay, there's a bunch of people there.
Holy shit.
Okay, not bad.
I still got it.
I thought maybe I was getting a little rusty here but no no no I've got the Noida skill still.
Now I just need the Noida knowledge to put that skill to use.
That's my only problem.
Oh, that's metal.
Shit.
Okay.
Of course first things first we got to get through the hemisphere and collect all the basic stuff.
Collect some wands, get some gold.
You know, set myself up for a potential amazing future here.
Okay, that dude right there needs to be killed with a tablet.
Because I just cannot deal with him.
What is that bottle down there?
It's toxic sludge.
Maybe we'll just shoot him.
Hey, that worked!
He must have lost some HP somehow before I started on him.
What's that?
What's green slimy meat?
Weird.
I'll take that.
Because oh watch this.
This is how you make this potion into... Oh, that's so genius.
Watch this guys.
Wait a minute, why do my keybinds not work?
Oh, they do work.
I just forgot them.
I gotta find water.
Watch this.
I'm gonna empty a little bit.
Then I go here, fill it up and now my... You see that?
Now that's water.
We have a double water potion now.
That's how you quickly get rid of the toxic sludge in there.
Okay, so I can't go this way.
I gotta go down and to the right to get the tablet.
It's gotta be in here.
Berserkium, nice!
I'm blessed with all the things.
I can get through there.
Whoops.
Actually, that may work.
Yeah, that's gonna burn this side.
I can get through.
And while we wait for that, I'm gonna get rid of the toxic shit.
Or I can just go below.
That's annoying.
I'm gonna wait for him to come up here.
Nice.
Feels good to be back in Noisa, man.
I gotta say that the controls really are immaculate.
You know, it's just so smooth and fluid.
Even though it's been a couple days here, or like almost a week, I still have it down, you know?
Order that.
Oh no!
Leave me alone.
Gold!
I struck gold!
Very nice.
That's a good start here.
I have to remember, consume the Berserkium.
Don't let it sit in the bottle.
I do wonder if Berserkium works with throwing the tablet.
Got it.
Now we're ready for anything.
Okay, what's happening down here?
Drink a bit of Berserkium?
Sometimes there's a heart right next to the portal, so you gotta check it out.
Whoa!
Okay, not too bad.
Give me that gold.
And I'll turn this into water.
Oh, another thing I want to do is try to mix more things together.
I have a cookbook going, right?
So I gotta try and mix things.
Oh, don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
Shit.
Mix it!
Why won't it mix?
Come on.
Weird.
Okay, better than nothing.
I feel like usually that makes us way faster.
Did he just shoot his friend?
It looked like it.
Incredible.
No.
I'm gonna blow this up.
Just do it.
Water myself.
Hey, miss.
Good to see you.
It's been a while.
Hey, miss.
Okay, at least the presence of enemies that are not dead is gonna guide me to where I haven't been, you know?
I can't rely on the vision part right now, because everything is dark.
A chest.
Nice.
I can get in there.
But first, we gotta turn it into water.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
What a shot.
The first one I found today.
Awesome.
Thanks.
Oh, I gotta pick this up.
What's that?
Snow plus soil pouch.
You know what?
That's great, because I was gonna try and mix things.
That's perfect.
Uh, get rid of the empty water bottle for now.
Give me that.
So what's in here?
Snow and soil plus grass.
Let's just try and mix some shit.
Put it all in there.
And then we put some water in there.
And then we put some berserkum in there.
Mix it up good.
A healthy snack for Jack.
Okay.
Wait, did I make peat?
Or is this peat?
No, that's swamp.
Okay.
I didn't do anything, unfortunately.
More snow.
All right.
Now we get the chest.
Please let it be a heart.
Oops.
Very good.
That's exactly what I needed.
Like the game almost new.
Oh yeah, that's gonna burn.
That's fine.
So I need to collect more materials, because now I have a pouch.
What's in it now?
Snow.
You know what?
Snow is just water, I guess.
Let's get rid of snow.
I kind of just want to get some different stuff.
Some coal, some whatever.
In fact, maybe just run around with it open and see what I can pick up.
Coal, moss.
Oh, look at moss.
Grass.
Coal, grass, soil, moss.
All kinds of things.
Can I pick up mushrooms?
Oh yeah, I can.
I can pick up the mushrooms you can get high on.
I know that one.
Pick up all of this.
Pick up some of this as well.
The more things I put in here, the bigger the chance of some kind of reaction happening when I mix it in the end, right?
All right, nothing here.
Okay, let's keep going.
Oh, that's a dead end.
Yeah, I don't know where I've been.
Okay, so it's not quite... Oh no, I'm stuck.
Fine, I'm fine.
I gotta use my tablet more.
Whoa.
Oh wow, he stopped the momentum of it by shooting it.
What an asshole.
Dude, I cannot hit anything.
My aim is off.
I gotta drink this berserkium to carry me.
Apparently, I can't kill anything.
I need all the help I can get.
Load that up.
It would be awesome if I could find just one more heart.
And maybe, maybe even just one more wand, please.
Uno mas por favor.
Oh, what?
I didn't even see you.
A little sneaky bugger.
I'm at 38 HP.
That's a bit risky.
Make some more of this.
Collapsed mines.
Should I really be here is the question.
Probably... What's that?
Oh, I'm on fire.
Fuck!
No, no, that's not water.
This is... I need to change this.
Oh my god.
That was almost a catastrophe.
In fact, it may be enough of a catastrophe that I just go.
Seven... I want to find an extra wand.
Is that too much to ask?
Just one more.
I only found a single.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck!
I can't get the right bottle out.
Oh, I may die here.
Let's just go.
Yeah, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
That was a bit of a disaster there at the end.
Oh, nice.
This is already looking great.
Oh, before we buy anything.
Let's see.
I like that.
I don't think I like that.
And maybe I don't like that, but I like this.
That's great.
Extra damage, but increased cast delay.
That's totally fine with me.
I'm getting that one.
And this is a shuffle wand, but I don't really care.
Or do I?
It does have a very low mana recharge.
Yeah, that's very slow.
That's very slow.
Oh man.
This is why I need to find an extra wand.
Precisely because of this.
I'm gonna take a bunch of these things.
Maybe even that one.
Yeah, I don't want the egg.
Maybe the vertical barrier, we can have some fun with that.
It's not amazing.
Maybe it is better on this one.
Ah, it's gotta, it's gotta be that one.
Like what are the chances of us shooting that 20 times in a row?
Pretty much nil, right?
It's not gonna happen.
And I think this can stay as it is.
Bomb is fine to have.
Sparkbolt could be...
Nah, that's actually crap.
It could put in this.
Not bad.
Yeah, it's gonna go here.
Okay, that's a bit of digging there.
And we have no way of getting out of here, do we?
No, so we just gotta go.
Just gotta go.
Also hold on, I gotta move my thingy away here on the table.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's see what we got.
Yep.
I want to say that this spell that I have right now is actually the... a freaking ideal spell for this level.
It's just perfect.
I love having the chain bolt here.
It does amazing damage.
It always hits the enemies.
It's foolproof, you know, even for someone like me.
And you can shoot through walls.
What's not to love?
I really want to try and minimize my damage taken here so I can go to the fungal caverns.
And get some exploration in there.
Now I can dig if I need to, but I won't do it here.
Maybe here.
Looks like a good spot.
Haha, I wasn't even trying to hit you.
Why won't I get... come on.
There we go.
Okay, there's bound to be some hearts here.
Mark my words.
It's gonna happen.
Also cheers everybody.
It's freaking Sunday.
Now I have a timer set so that my beard doesn't freeze over in the freezer.
So I got to take it out at some point.
Something in there?
Wait a minute.
Why is there a little spot there?
What do I see?
Show me the goods.
No, I don't see anything.
Sometimes they like to hide the hearts inside of small pockets.
Cool.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look at that.
There's writing there.
I never noticed.
You know what that means.
We got to translate.
So it's the musical note and the diamond.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on.
Musical note and diamond.
Let's see what this says.
Musical note is where?
Musical note.
It is?
Did I ever find it?
Oh yeah, it's T.
So we have T and then we have this diamond shape or O.
Is E teleport?
Is it going to say teleport?
And then the next one is this weird thing.
Okay.
Back.
So the weird thing is the weird thing is what is that?
Is it?
Is it one?
Is it a capital letter?
It's an L, but it's a capital letter.
What the hell?
Okay.
And then E again.
Yeah.
Teleport.
Teleport's got to say teleport.
And then we have an X.
P. Unless, hold on.
Unless it's all in capital letters.
Let's see here.
Oh yeah.
Maybe it's all in capital actually.
Let's see the E in capital.
Oh yeah, it is.
It is.
I'm a dumbass.
Oh, that's lovely.
Get rid of this.
Tele.
Let's see.
Let's just confirm.
X.
Is it P?
It is.
Oh my God.
I don't know why I'm so surprised.
It's just awesome.
And then we have the B, which is an O.
Yeah.
Teleport.
Then we have the thingy thingy.
If you have no idea what I'm talking about, that's fine.
It's an R.
Yeah.
And then we have another T.
Right?
Let me check.
Yep.
Teleport!
Hey!
Pretty cool.
So that one and the E.
That one.
The big L.
Rest in peace to big L.
And then we have E again.
And a big P. And then the O, which is this weird thingy.
And another R.
No, the first R, which is this thing.
And then a T again.
Cool!
Ha ha ha!
My first successful translation.
Hey!
We can speak the language of the Neuschians?
How cool is that?
That's amazing.
Really nice.
It's like that meme of the guy looking in the back, you know?
And it's like, I don't know what I expected.
I mean, it makes sense that it says teleport.
This also says teleport.
I can read.
I don't even need my alphabet anymore.
I can just read the text now.
Mark my words.
Well, not really, but almost.
Almost.
We're almost there.
I won!
Magic arrow.
Not that great.
Gotta be honest here, that's very underwhelming.
But it's fine.
I shall have more opportunities in the fungal caverns.
For the fungal caverns, I have great loot.
Nice.
What's happening there?
Oh yeah, I knew that was gonna hit me.
I just knew it.
I don't like this fire falling from the sky.
What is that?
Hold on, so there's a gold noggin that's blocking my vision here.
I need to wait for it to go away.
It's coal and rock.
Okay.
Coal and rock.
Wait, do we have a... do we have a worm?
This looks like the... no, that looks like...
That's acid.
Oh my god, I can't even speak.
I can get through here.
So good.
Which case I can switch to this for combat, actually.
If I run out of mana here.
No!
Nah!
Fucking acid.
Or toxic sludge.
I mean, get it out of my face.
Is the audio bugging already?
I just had an audio glitch, I think.
Hopefully there's no crashing.
Yeah, nice.
Pete and Swamp.
Why is Pete generated?
I wonder.
Pete, Pete, Pete.
I think I googled what Pete was once, but I forgot.
It's some sort of dirty water, I think.
It's just dirty water.
Nasty water.
Crusty water.
Come on, man.
Show me the wants.
Or the hearts or something.
I need it, yo.
What kind of a welcome is this in the game of Noita after this long time?
What's happening there?
I think I found a gravitational anomaly.
Oh, never mind.
Okay, it fell off.
That was a bit odd.
Okay.
I think we gotta go to the fungal caverns.
There's nothing for me here.
I have 800 gold.
That's very respectable.
But I could want some more.
Okay, that wasn't worth it.
I could have gone around it.
Ah.
Whoops.
Wait, what's hiding up here?
Nothing.
So I've been here.
Let me go below and then left.
At least it's not dark here, like the hemisphere.
How was this one, by the way?
Two slots.
It's shit.
We need something better for the next holy mountain in case we find some great spells.
Also, I'm gonna get high, dude.
We're gonna get high.
We're gonna get so high when I get to the fungal caverns.
In fact, we're gonna get high three times.
Can I really not get there?
Actually, hold on.
Do I need to dig?
I mean, I guess there's coal.
It's not the worst thing.
We can get through here.
Okay,
let me check up here as well.
See, here we go.
Oh man.
But I guess it's better than that.
At least it has slots on it.
I can throw eggs if I want to.
Eggs.
Egg.
The eggs are just not that cool.
The broken wand.
Oh.
I'm gonna make my way in like this.
I'm gonna get rid of this pouch, I guess.
I gotta take the broken wand and I gotta keep the berserkium.
Okay, here we go.
We're actually at the center of the level now.
I thought it was more to the left.
Wait, where did this guy go?
Oh, here.
No, wait, what?
He did a Houdini.
I need some more water.
Okay.
Yo, what's happening here?
This wooden construction looks mysterious to me.
I don't know if I've seen this before.
That looks new.
And the game keeps throwing new things at me here lately.
Also, last time I found the dice.
And it turns out, fucking Einstein was wrong.
He said the gods do not play dice.
Apparently they do in this game.
Formation...
Burst of... I think... I would rather have that than this, honestly.
I mean, they're both kind of meh.
Wait, I'm low on mana.
Goddamn.
Definitely gonna change my want with the chain bolt on it soon.
Now we're talking!
Yes!
Fantastic!
This is big.
Except... Oh, the recharge on it is painful.
Better than nothing, though.
Better than nothing.
Wait, why am I... Oh, I see.
I see.
We made it.
I know I can just teleport through here, but I'm doing it for safety reasons, so I can walk out in case I need to.
Oh, what the... How dare you?
No!
Ah, shit.
All right, we're committed now.
What's that?
Oh, it's slime.
It looked like a broken wand.
My chain bolt wand needs to recharge, man.
It's so bad right now.
Oh, energy orb.
That's big.
But it's with a timer, so it costs a lot of mana.
Explosion on slimy enemies.
This is the place for it, I guess.
Formation behind your back.
Huh.
Weird.
Can I get through here?
Is that all steel?
I guess it is.
Okay, we gotta be ultra careful here.
Let's find a way out again in case we get into a problem here, because everything can go from a hundred... no, from a zero to a hundred, really fast in this spot.
So we're just gonna be digging here.
Gonna make a little emergency exit.
And look at that, we've got a man.
The man himself.
Ow!
Ah, you asshole.
Ah, you're so annoying.
Where the hell am I?
What's that?
Teleportation.
I don't want it.
I gotta go back to the caverns.
Okay, I finally killed him.
Or did I or did he teleport?
He may have teleported.
Did that say ethereal meat?
Huh.
Weird.
You can eat it and then you also teleport.
That's the thing I also figured out last time.
You can control that teleport with your cursor.
Actually a big discovery.
You can use it to get in and out of holy mountains.
Get another method of doing that.
Oh, don't you hit me with that.
Ah, fuck.
They're so annoying.
Please.
Where are you?
Where did you go?
Flammoxium?
No, I don't think so.
Okay, I killed him.
Oh!
I think that's a dude that makes me blind.
What's this?
Heavy spread.
That's actually a big one.
I like having this.
That makes digging really nice.
But I gotta...
No,
I'll leave it here.
I'd rather have my energy orb.
And I need this one in case my number one one runs out of mana.
But I guess this does do damage in a pinch.
And the heavy spread is only really useful when I have something like a digging bolt.
Oh, fuck off.
It's so dark here also.
I can't see this guy.
It's really, really dangerous for Circum.
That's okay.
Oh, hello.
Hello, sir.
Got him.
What's this here?
I don't... I'm not intrigued by that.
Okay, there's nothing here.
Destroy that.
Oh, no, no.
Fuck.
That's the one I wanted to use.
Also, we're at 53 HP.
This is pushing it a little bit.
We gotta find some drugs and get out.
But a big chunk of it, not just this small potatoes here.
We gotta really, you know, get to it.
I guess I could start eating this.
Eat the drugs.
Rate their lap and then leave.
Nice.
And a double spell.
Let's take it.
I think that's worth it.
That's a good one.
I could never go wrong with the chainsaw.
Uh-oh.
This guy I'm scared of.
Oh, I'm out of mana now.
See, this is the issue.
Switch this back for now.
Give me that money.
I saw another one, yeah, right below me.
Right below me.
It's gonna take a while to get to that.
But hold on.
Chainsaw's not gonna do anything.
Okay.
Dude, the energy.
Oh, oh.
Oh, no.
Fuck.
We gotta leave.
Yeah, no, no, no.
We're leaving.
Oh, wait, there's wands here, though.
Maybe just these wands and then I'm out.
Oh, I can't get in here.
Unless I can't?
Yes.
Potion?
It just says potion.
What?
What the hell's going on?
Oh, that's that one.
Uh, it also lost my chain bolt.
I'm gonna die here.
I gotta go back for my chain bolt.
Please don't kill me.
Where is this man?
Where is he?
Where's my wand?
Wait, is it here?
Somewhere?
Fuck.
Where's my wand?
I don't see it.
I think it's gone.
I don't know where... someone picked it up, I think.
Someone ran off with it.
Ah, there's also a wand up here.
Just quickly have a peek.
Just, just... oh, hold on.
I want!
Okay, not bad, I guess.
And then the last thing...
Here we go, we go, we go now.
But wait, I wanted to get high.
I guess we can get high later.
Right, we can get high later.
Ah, shit, this place is so deadly.
Now I just need to get to the end without dying here.
Unfortunately, I lost my chain bolt.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Go.
Okay.
All right.
Damn, that's a lot.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, I'm taking that.
We're gonna be invisible.
That's a big one.
Let's see here.
This wand is very mediocre.
But we do have heavy spread, so we can probably do something cool here.
Or even that.
A little bit ran there.
I should probably be using this one for that.
Damn, that's, that's a lot of spread.
That's better.
Oh, I run out of mana?
Oh, the heavy spread costs mana, right.
That's actually not bad.
Anyway, let's see here.
Maybe I should go with a, I mean, my best option right now is a triplicate bolt wand, I think.
Also, what wand do we have here?
What is the stats like?
They're all fucking shuffle.
That sucks.
Okay.
Maybe I do this.
Oh, wait, a shuffle, of course.
Yeah, it's still a mystery to me how exactly this works.
The recharge time is the limiting factor here.
So, we don't need three of these.
Teleport is done.
That's good.
Although it's on a shitty wand, so let's put it on something better.
Maybe that one.
This is now my teleport.
That's solid.
That's really good.
Now, damage, unfortunately, we don't have.
That's the big problem.
How does that perform?
Very badly.
Also, I do have a wand with an extra one of these.
Let's take this as well.
I mean, that's not bad, I guess.
Maybe if I do a double on it, didn't I have that?
Just get a bit more damage in there sometimes.
So, recharge time is quite high now, but this one reduces it.
But not in the way you think.
It's always a little bit finicky or like complicated.
How exactly that works.
See, that's already better.
Not bad there.
That's nice.
Compare that to this.
Much faster.
Well, not much faster, but it is definitely faster.
It's faster.
Pompompompomp.
Okay, that's not good.
What if I add this one at the end?
And one of them gets shot like that.
Ah, that's bad, that's bad.
Unless I can dummy this on...
something.
Can I dummy that on... can I dummy that on the projectile?
Wait, on this one.
Oh, but no, wait, this is gonna affect this one as well in that case.
What if I do this?
That's definitely better.
So, if I add two of them, it doesn't actually do much there.
It does have 0.75 recharge time, which is a lot.
I mean, this is... it's like, it's so much work to make a wand that is so shitty even, you know?
This wand is so bad.
It's a horrible wand.
I shouldn't have thrown away my chain bolt.
Fuck, why did I do that?
That was so dumb.
I want to make the other version I had here.
This one.
That's the best.
All right, that's my damage, that's my teleport, and then we need some digging.
And, I mean, this already digs, I guess.
Yeah, maybe the vertical barrier is something we can play with.
Worst case, I lose it, I don't care.
I could go with some of these.
The disc projectiles.
Especially because I have concentrated spells.
That means they're not gonna shoot in an arc very much.
Could be cool.
Let's try it.
That shoots three at a time, huh?
That's actually a good amount of burst there.
Hold up, do we have something that shoots more than three?
Four?
Six.
Ooh, hold up.
Throw that there.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
One second recharge though, so this is the ultimate shotgun.
That's scary.
If that hits me, I'm toast.
But, you know, think about it.
We go around, we're invisible, and we go puff.
Someone dies.
This is just, this is, what is that?
That's like 120 damage, if I hit with everything.
Not the worst.
Okay, let's go.
I'm invisible, yoink, and I miss.
Let me
go around like this.
It is nice for scouting out areas, I guess, like this.
Then, how do I want to fight you?
I don't think so.
How good am I at killing you?
I gotta test this.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Very dope.
Oh, nice.
What a boon.
Hello, sir.
Hey, hey.
No, no, make me invisible.
Gotcha.
A shiny orb.
That's about it.
No more.
It's gonna explode at some point.
Now, I don't like that.
Wow, he's shooting rats!
They're shooting each other?
Now what?
What's happening there?
Get out of the way.
Oh, shit.
All of his friends.
I swear to god, these projectiles, they always hit me.
I'm almost, I'm almost dead already.
Fuck, man.
We need polymorphine.
No, we need, what is it called?
Pheromone.
For the next level.
And I'm bloody as hell and it won't go away, so I can't go invisible.
I need to find that perk that makes me go... or shake off the liquids faster.
This is actually, no, it only has two slots.
It's not very good.
Six shot there.
There's a wand.
Ah, too much blood.
That's actually a decent wand for a digging wand.
I'll let go of that one to get it.
Doesn't seem bad.
Oh, man.
Man, the disc projectiles are really taking care of the robots.
Or at least the robotic enemies.
I want to get this liquid off.
I did 300 something damage there.
How is that possible?
They do 20 damage each and I shoot six of them.
Maybe I crit them.
Ambrosia.
That's nice.
Sometimes this game, man, it just trolls you.
No!
Wrong!
Oh, what?
Oh my god.
I actually ended up killing myself with the saw blades.
That was like a chain of bad things happening.
I was using my teleport wand when I thought I was using my saw blade wands.
And then I accidentally teleported into him.
I panic switched to saw blades, shot him, and the saw blades bounced off and killed me.
Yeah.
That's a classic.
And when I say classic, I mean, it's something I've never experienced before, but you expect it to happen.
You know what I mean?
Like in this game, you should always expect the unexpected, which is impossible to do.
That's why it's unexpected.
Is there sometimes a heart down here?
Don't think so.
I don't think I've ever seen one down there.
Hello!
Okay.
What's that?
Room stone of magma.
Have I tried that one before?
What does that mean?
Magma, meaning fire.
What is it?
It says fire to things?
Oh, yeah.
It says fire to me.
Yeah.
Okay.
Is that what's happening?
Hold on.
Oh, yeah.
Look, it is setting fire to things.
Weird.
Slime potion.
We got to try that stone somewhere else.
Yo.
Look at this.
Wait a minute.
Oh, wow.
It turns everything into lava.
A bit dangerous.
Oh, my God.
That's actually amazing.
Look at this.
Instantly turned into...
So it reacted with the water, I guess, or what was in here, and it made this lava stone.
There's something down here.
Well, that's a recipe for getting yourself killed, I think.
I don't think I should be using that much.
Especially because if I'm wet... Hold on.
Is that just going to automatically put me on fire?
Let me not be wet here before I throw it.
Let's get to safety first.
There we go.
Ah, fuck.
Come on.
Get it off.
Okay, now.
Yeah, look, I'm safe.
I'm safe.
But if I go here now...
Actually, kind of cool.
I wonder how I can use that to my advantage.
What if I do it now?
It's a fun toy.
I like this toy.
Also, look at it.
It actually has a symbol on it.
You see that?
I do wonder.
Hold on.
Is that fire?
Huh.
I think it may be.
Oh, and a heart.
Either fire or lava, I guess.
Oh, let
me just wait for that.
And while I wait, I'm just going to have a bit of fun with my new toy.
I guess I could also throw it into the face of someone.
Like him.
Hold on.
He's made of... Uh-oh.
Uh-oh.
Oh, wait.
I'm water.
Pick it up.
I mean, maybe it doesn't matter if I'm water or not.
Please die.
His babies are more dangerous than himself.
I see the hymns.
No, that's not a hymns.
That's a guy.
Whoa.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Nobody's angry.
That's good.
Not yet.
Lava potion.
Let me just do a bit of this.
Everything is lava.
Maybe I shouldn't make everything into lava.
You know, on paper, it sounds bad, because lava is bad.
So why am I doing it?
I don't know.
It's one of those mysteries.
Flammoxium.
I'll take it.
Let's try and make some things.
Let's try slime.
Oh, that actually makes hell slime.
What?
Wait a minute.
Is that real?
Hold up.
So there's slime in here now.
Watch.
Hell slime.
Slime plus lava.
And you get hell slime.
I wonder what properties that has.
I want to try and make a big batch of it.
Okay, let me try flammoxium in here.
I need a new pool of lava.
We gotta try and put different things into lava.
It's like a very important substance.
He's on fire and he died.
Nice.
Whoa.
Oh, it's oh my god.
That dynamite hit me right on the nose.
Uh, I'm in a bit of a pickle here.
Come here.
That's gonna explode for sure.
Also, I'm oiled up right now.
What is that?
Whoa.
My potion is steam.
No.
That's bad.
I gotta find some proper water.
I guess, I guess because of all the lava shenanigans that I did.
Yo, that is a sick wand.
Too bad it's shuffle.
Water, water, water.
I see more water.
I want a rune stone of gold.
Something where it emits an aura that turns everything into gold.
That's what I want.
Is that too much to ask?
Just a simple rune stone of gold.
Can I has it?
What's this?
It's copper.
I mean, we're kind of low HP here.
Maybe it's time to leave.
Uh-oh, there's a frog.
This is not coming after me.
Man, nothing over here.
I want a bit more gold.
Uh-oh, I see you there.
I'm gonna confuse you.
Get flummoxed.
He's so confused.
Get, uh, slimed.
And watered.
Then we're gonna set fire to you.
Oh, shit.
No.
I called that, by the way.
I was gonna die to that.
I knew it was gonna be my death at some point.
I just knew it.
I just have that feeling.
People are already going at it down there.
Dude, I am not getting far in this game.
Holy shit.
I need to go slower.
But it's so much fun to experiment with new toys.
How can you not?
Bop.
Oh, maybe that's a bad idea.
Thanks.
Okay, we're gonna go even slower now.
And try to make non-bad decisions.
I know.
Sounds crazy.
But I'm doing my best.
That's a dead end for sure.
I'm gonna avoid the fire.
See, that's an example of a non-bad decision.
We're gonna make more of those.
This is the good decision right here.
Turning this into water.
So far, we have only made good decisions.
So, if you were to draw a little line on a white board where you have bad decisions and good decisions, I would have three good decisions already and zero bad decisions.
The Hemesis.
Okay, see, that was a bad decision going in there.
I should have gone the other way.
That's the line in the bad decision.
Play it safe.
Play it at the distance.
Use the terrain to your... Ooh, look, a toy!
I
may be doing some bad decisions here, but it's all in the name of science.
So, this is the exact same type of dice as I saw earlier.
This is not a different one.
It does the same thing.
I'm taking it with me.
In fact, I want to try and offer that up to the gods,
but I need a way to get up first.
Thank you.
A broken wand.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, multiple Hemesis.
I need something to dig with so I can get up on the top of the mountain.
If you're prone off, you maybe could do it with this, but you'd have to shoot it and then hit it with another spell in the air and time it.
No, it's not gonna happen.
There's no way.
What happened here?
Look at that.
That's not a worm.
That's a snake.
It's a very peculiar thing going on here.
No.
Hello.
And off he goes.
Yo, look at all the potions down there.
Oh no.
What is that?
What's with the wall here?
Meteorite.
Is that guy immune to lava?
What?
There we go.
Got him.
Okay.
This is my laboratory now.
This is where I shall perform experiments.
This is the perfect test environment.
Polymorphine.
Acceleration.
Flammoxium.
Ambrosia.
Pheromone.
Oh my god.
There's all the potions.
I'm gonna take... What do I have?
Acceleration.
Flammoxium.
Levitation.
That means I can get on top of the mountain.
Teleportation.
And I'm gonna take that too.
Oh, but I don't have dice.
And then I come back down here for more potions.
There's no way that gods can resist this lovely chaotic die.
Here it is.
Okay.
70 seconds.
Look, it's so misty out here.
And on the plus side, I also get some health.
Oh dude, I can go grab the demon eye now as well.
Dude, we can translate this.
It's translation time.
Let's see what it says.
Get back to this one.
Let's put that up here for now.
So it's a four and a thingy.
So a four.
I wonder if it's in all caps again.
B.
And then we have the R.
And then we have a weird seven upside down.
Oh, that's I.
Brie.
Now we have the P.
Bring.
Then we have that thing, which is... Yeah, bring.
Something.
Bring.
And then we have the... Is that a note?
T.
And we have N.
Wait.
No, bring, T, R.
Hold on.
T.
Am I reading that wrong?
B, R, I, and G.
Oh, I am reading it wrong.
It's an F.
Hold on.
It's the F symbol.
Or is it the R symbol?
Could be considered... No, it's an F symbol for sure.
But I don't have that.
That's something I haven't found.
Okay, so we don't know what that is.
Let's just keep going.
The square.
I don't think I found that one either.
So question mark, question mark.
Unless...
I'm thinking bring the... Maybe the square is the same as this.
In this case, it's just rotated.
Uh, let's see here.
Do we have H?
H is that one, which is R.
But it looks like an F here.
But maybe that's the thing.
Maybe it is the same.
I'm gonna assume this says bring the.
Because it is three letters.
And then here comes a new word.
And then T.
And then we have R again.
Bring the true.
Then we have the... Oh yeah, it's gotta be treasure.
It's gotta be in treasure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This thing means A.
Tri... Is that an S coming after that?
That's the arrow.
Arrow, arrow, arrow.
It is, it is.
Bring the... I'm just gonna assume treasure.
Bring the treasure.
And then we have... H.
R.
Bring the treasure here.
Hey!
That's what it says.
Bring the treasure here.
Well, that's exactly what I've done.
Watch!
Whoops.
That's not good.
I'm sorry for vandalizing your temple.
Oh wait, that's the cold stuff.
Is everyone dead?
Okay, I guess that did nothing.
What if I put this here?
Dude, I figured out bring the treasure here before I even translated it.
Also, I can't even see the text anymore.
It's actually illegible at this point.
Okay, let's see if we can't get in there.
We only have five of these.
Ah, may not be enough.
Hopefully, we can use the chaos dice to get the rest.
Is that gonna explode?
Let's see.
No!
Not, not, no!
My dice.
I'm not getting it, am I?
I'm not getting that.
Let me go grab it again.
Thank you.
Get back up.
Let's try again.
I'm gonna gently put it down.
Okay, not bad.
Oops, that's bad.
That's freezing vapor.
Let's wait it out.
Also, I can eat all this.
We can get high right now.
Oh yeah.
Oh, oh yeah, baby.
What's with the colors?
It's all completely fucked.
It's usually not this fucked.
Is that enough?
Oh my god.
Blood.
Okay.
No!
I hate when it spawns these things.
Almost there.
Oh no.
This is the most scuffed way to get in here.
Oh fuck.
I barely can see anything here.
It's...
Go!
Oh, it activated down here because it technically rolled.
I'm too committed here, guys.
I need, I need to get in.
Can I put it a little bit more...
to the left?
Oh!
Ew!
I hate that!
No!
Hit it.
I'm actually dying here.
I'm not getting in.
Get me in!
Oh wait, I can shoot my way in.
Oh my god, I can't shoot my way in!
No way, bro.
I, I guess it is just ice.
Oh!
Oh, we're getting high.
We're getting high.
Guys,
we're about to be on cloud nine here.
No!
Whoa!
One HP!
Okay, dude.
There's nothing else to do but get high, I guess, at this point.
At this point, come on.
Weird fungus, huh?
I don't know if I can get high already, but we can try.
If I eat the wrong thing here, I die.
Just the smallest wrong thing in my mouth and I'm dead.
I'm stuck, I'm stuck, I'm stuck!
No!
Let me out!
I'm gonna eat my way out.
I can't.
Okay, there we go, there we go.
Oh, shit, dude.
Oh, fuck.
That's the good stuff.
Oh, that's my alarm.
Hold on.
I gotta go get my, my drink.
Cheers, everybody.
Oh man, I'm just vomiting here.
Man, look at all that vomit, huh?
This is nasty.
The usual concepts don't apply.
Look at how it's, I think it's trying to transform right now.
But the cooldown has not, has not gone away yet.
Can I pick up, I need, I need, I need a pouch to pick this up.
At least I know where to go if I need to get high.
I think it's time to just go through the portal.
We have a bit of money.
Oh, but we're so high, we can't even see straight.
This is gonna be a challenge to get through.
If I touch the wrong pixel here, I'm dead.
What's that?
Toxic sludge.
That's what I mean, like the simplest mistake here, and I'm out.
Okay.
What's that?
Water.
Okay.
Better stay hydrated here.
Maybe I pick something up on the way down.
Maybe get rid of levitation and get unstable
teleportation.
Accelerate.
Don't we have a normal teleportation, please?
Concentrated mana.
Phamoxium pheromone.
Damn it.
That's not what I want.
I guess I'll take pheromone.
That is pheromone, right?
It is.
Go.
1 HP.
Oh, damn.
Okay.
I don't know what got transformed.
It said blood.
Nice.
We got a good one here.
And we got teleport.
Oh, big.
Is this projectile slower?
Stainless armor.
That's a good one.
I'm taking that.
I'll take this one then.
Just to get one of these.
Let's keep that up there.
What else should I take here?
They're all shuffled.
What is going on?
Ah!
I should have bought this instead of the other.
God damn it.
I messed up again.
Oh, but you know what?
That's actually solid.
I can run with that.
That's totally okay.
Totally okay.
I'm gonna come back for that.
Oh, am I though?
I can't come back for it unless I take the wand with me.
So that means I gotta leave at least one slot open.
If only I had teleportation.
Okay, let's go.
At least I'm not high anymore.
Whoa!
Oh my god!
And this one sucks.
The recharge is always worse than you think.
When you tried it, when you test it, you shoot a couple of shots of it and you're like, ah, that's good.
But in a real world situation, it's not that great.
What's this?
Copper pouch.
I mean, it would be nice to get that pouch and bring the fungus with me upstairs.
I guess.
Oh, he has a wand.
Three people have had this wand in the span of six seconds.
Damn.
What a chaotic one.
There's some good stuff on here.
I don't think I want to go to a fungal caverns.
I may have to adapt my strategy to come back there later and perform my experiments because it's just too dangerous early on unless you have a really good setup.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Fuck you.
Okay.
It's actually an okay wand if you just pace yourself.
Let it recharge a little bit.
Use it in bursts.
Is there a mom somewhere here?
Like these guys keep coming in a weird line as if they're being spawned.
Amazing shot.
I applaud you.
Well done.
It even arced and everything to hit me.
Really well done there.
Okay, yeah, I definitely need more money before I go in there.
Can I scrounge some potions from this guy?
I'm gonna try.
Vomits?
Transformed.
Wait, has blood become vomit?
Is that what's happening?
Also, these guys are completely immune to lava.
Like that's just that's just what they are.
They're immune.
Where's that?
Pheromone.
I kind of want to try and put pheromone on all kinds of enemies.
Who wants to get pheromone?
Okay, maybe... don't do it when there's a million people.
I'm gonna die here, probably.
Can I please just get a second?
Do I have any way of digging?
I do have a very risky way of digging.
I'm doing it.
Okay, that works.
That works, baby.
Give me money.
Don't burn me though.
Okay, 500 gold.
Not bad.
I'm just gonna go through the portal.
Don't even care about the...
What?
Why have I angered them?
Why?
Oh, but look at this here.
That's big.
It's very big.
Let me get that.
Let me see if I can't snipe a perk down here that I want.
What do we got?
Nothing that I want, I don't think.
So I'm gonna have to reroll that.
You fucking asshole.
Come here.
Is he shooting the fish?
Run!
Sure.
Just do it.
Problem is, I don't have any weapons.
My arsenal is shite.
No idea how that guy got angered.
It's a weird situation.
Can a man just not anger the gods, please, for once?
I'm gonna go this way.
The problem is, we're gonna have a steward in every holy mountain from now on.
I almost just want to kill myself.
I don't even want to continue this run.
I mean, maybe I'll get lucky and find something crazy.
You never know.
Especially now that I have all division in the world, maybe I'll see something that will turn everything around for me.
I doubt it though.
Let
me go over here.
Yeah, I can't kill these guys, unfortunately.
That's just not something I can do.
I need to find... What do I need to find?
Something big and something that goes boom.
So I can really nail the gods.
Oh, look, it's this.
Oh, wait, wait.
That means blood.
Whoa.
But hold on.
I can't get blood because it's vomit.
I can't even get blood.
Actually, there is blood here.
No, that's not blood.
That's just blood stains.
Yeah, look, all of this is vomit.
Shit.
I'm going to quickly scout through the level now that I have all division to see if we can't find a nice heart.
I guess that's something you should be doing if you have all this vision.
It's a bit risky.
But with all this teleport, it's kind of nice.
I want.
Thanks.
Uh oh.
I hear scary things.
Let's go this way.
Also, a lot of HP.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
So I got to be fat.
As soon as I go through the portal, Stewart's going to be waiting.
What's in here?
Actually, all kinds of shit.
I like it.
Um.
Goddamn.
All right, Stewart.
Show me what you got.
Dude, sheep.
You know what?
I'm going to snatch that.
Wait, somehow I didn't take damage there.
I don't know how that happened.
Oh, wait.
Did I not even?
I didn't get it.
Fuck.
Give me a moment.
Please give me a moment.
Put it down gently.
Oh my god.
Don't.
Crap, crap, crap, crap, crap.
I got it.
Okay, okay, okay.
So my whole game plan right now is to avoid the gods and just find, just skip through the levels with teleport.
Hoping for a Hail Mary.
That's really all it is.
Wait, what?
Oh, shit.
Yeah, right.
I don't have a primary wand anymore.
That's right.
I forgot about that.
I guess I have this one.
Hey!
Gold I can use.
Thank you.
A thousand even.
Not bad.
That's fully cooked meat right there.
I shall be playing the game of avoiding and not killing.
Which is kind of nuts.
I know, but hear me out.
I'm gonna go down and to the forge or whatever.
Sweet.
How do I kill this guy?
There we go.
We actually have a friendo.
Wait, I gotta kill these guys.
No!
Burn alive.
Sir?
Okay.
Hey, this is so scuffed.
Show me.
What is this?
It's trash.
My Hail Mary.
Wasn't that great?
Okay, but I'm not done with this level.
I'm looking for hearts.
This is, this is getting very, very not great.
I was electrocuted.
Chaotic.
Oh, what?
Oh, got shot from off screen.
While this run was rib anyway.
Like the gods got angered for who knows what reason.
Couldn't really do much.
When the gods get angered, you end your life.
That's okay.
I'm having to start a new run actually.
That was a shitshow.
A pure shitshow.
There was poop everywhere.
Feces left and right.
I can't help but wonder.
There's something going on with this thing and I can't figure out what it is.
This looks like a disc.
Like a floppy disc.
You know, almost like a safe slot or something.
It's weird.
I cannot imagine what I have to do there.
Also, I do have water.
Brian potion.
That should work fine.
Against the fireman.
Oh, he died.
That's so lucky.
He went in the water.
Does he not even know that he can't go in there?
Remember, you don't have teleport.
You have the exploding crystals.
Do not teleport like a dummy now.
Thanks.
Put this here.
Very good.
Here's the tablet.
Get extra money.
Oh, look at all the.
Wow.
Rabbit.
There's so many.
I've never seen that many hemises.
Wow.
Insane shot there.
But I saw all that gold.
I saw I needed to get it, you know.
Look how much money already made just off of those hemises.
This is sponsored by him.
This run is sponsored by him.
If I see the all seeing eye perk again, I'm taking it.
Next.
Oh, that's close to touching.
Whoops.
Although.
No, that's too scary.
No, no, no.
How do I get around that?
I could just destroy it, I guess.
Oh, Hamis.
I love that thing.
What?
How?
Oh, come on.
Like, how did he not die from that throw?
It hit him straight in the face.
That's just not OK.
See, that one missed.
That was on me.
What's this?
Look, a shitty.
Actually, that's a great one, except that it's shuffle.
So all in all, kind of poopy.
This guy needs to die with a tablet.
Never mind.
What a violent explosion.
He also flew to Mars, apparently.
Also, I'm about to die, so yeah, there's that.
Don't hit me.
That tablet saved my life.
Teleportation.
Um.
Can I grab it in time?
Let's try.
Oh, I was quick.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Careful now.
OK, it's gone.
The hell's going on there?
Everyone's going for a swim here.
This is the communal bath.
Thank you.
I'm going to grab this wand, and then I think I'll maybe be on my way.
Actually, not a bad wand either.
But it's just shuffle.
It's just a thing.
It makes it really bad.
Notice this platform over here.
I'm getting Zelda vibes from this right now, and if you know, you know.
Breath of the Wild.
Hold on.
I don't even know how I would do that.
I think I have to put this thing up here to trigger something.
But it's electrifying, so how do I do that?
I don't think I can.
There's definitely a puzzle there.
It's like so obvious.
OK, I have 11 HP.
I think it's time we get the hell out of here.
Now just to get there without dying.
Eh, no.
Wait, that's not the path anyway.
Don't even do it.
That should be fine.
Go.
OK, not bad.
700 goldies?
In my pockets?
I likeies.
That one is good.
Oh, and teleport.
Oh, oh, this is a sick one.
What do we got?
Oh, we got kind of shitty ones.
Angry ghost and hungry ghost.
No, I don't like ghost.
Do what?
Maybe I like greed.
Or more love.
You gain double the gold, though?
That could be big, right?
I'm taking it.
We're being greedy.
Hand me that one.
Hand me...
that one.
Maybe a bit of this.
Also, I feel like my game is lagging.
Hold on, let me alt-tab out.
Do I have anything running in the background?
I have a couple things I can disable.
Let me disable that.
Let me disable...
That's fine.
How does it feel?
Still feels a little bit weird.
OK.
By the way, check this out.
Eh?
Is that too crazy?
It's only the first shot, actually.
And then after that, it's gonna be...
It's by design.
But I'm also thinking... OK, so these are all shuffled.
That's bad.
I think I... I was actually thinking about this.
You know?
And if I hit something with it, hopefully that projectile is not gonna come back at me.
OK, but maybe if it hits a real enemy, the projectile is not gonna come back at me.
There's a chance.
There's a chance that works that way.
And this one is a spitter bolt with timer.
What's that one?
Explosion of... What was that?
Just a fiery explosion.
Cost only 10 mana.
How about that?
Maybe not too bad.
I think I like it.
Or... Oh, actually.
Since this does seven damage in explosion, maybe it's better with this instead.
You know, just more damage.
Or, like, less risky damage.
But then again, if this can dig, then there's an argument to be made there that it could be nice to have.
So this is a little bit too slow mana regen.
I'm gonna use this instead.
Much better.
In fact, this one is really good.
So is that one.
We could put some stuff on this.
What if we go a little nuts?
That's not bad.
It's really not bad.
Let me mix some of this in.
No, actually recharge time is the one here.
So we actually only need a single.
That should make it better.
Hey!
That's not bad at all.
So if I do this...
Can I make this always... Let's think about this.
This is a shuffle wand.
Is there a way to always guarantee that it will be a trigger?
If it shoots this, then it does exactly what I want, because then it's gonna shoot that as well.
But if it triggers that one first, then it's not gonna work.
But if I use a double scatter...
Can it start here then?
If this is inside, let's see.
I guess it can.
Okay, so never mind.
If I do this...
Maybe that is just better overall.
But I do run out of mana quick, so there's that.
Let me see the overall damage here.
Okay, what about here?
That's actually not bad.
I think I like this the most out of all the things.
Then we have a teleport.
Very sweet.
And what else should I get?
Maybe a light.
I actually shoot faster here, because this one is looking for a projectile.
There's nothing, so it's gonna start over.
So it shoots two of these at once, and then it triggers the recharge.
So it goes pop-pop, pop-pop, pop-pop.
Cool.
That's nice.
And that's about it.
I think I'm good here.
We have greed.
We're gonna get lots of gold.
And this is a promising one.
Let's see how well this digs.
It does dig a little bit.
Well, it's not great.
Especially because this is coal, and it should really be digging through coal, like a knife through warm butter, but it's not doing that.
Yeah.
Okay.
The nice thing about it being an explosion is that there's AoE damage, which can be nice against clumps of enemies.
Like that.
Like, I just need to approximately hit them, and then they die, right?
Oh god.
Nice!
A heart for me.
Let me in.
Decently effective.
Hey, another one.
I will take it.
The explosion is kind of big and violent, but the damage it does is very small.
So there's a disconnect there between the visuals and the actual numbers, you know?
Chaotic polymorphine.
Yeah, I knew that was gonna happen.
Don't kill me.
I'm stuck in a pixel.
I feel like this explosion is way too volatile.
I will end up killing myself with it.
Unfortunately, we can't go back and change our wand.
Oh,
hello.
Polymorphine.
It is satisfying to shoot this wand, though.
Feels like the sort of gun that, I don't know, an APC would shoot.
Like, it's not quite a... Oh my god!
No, no, no.
Water myself.
And already we're almost dead.
Chaotic path.
It does add more speed to it.
Look at that, cast a lay of zero.
But again, it's just shuffle wand.
Honestly, I wish shuffle wasn't a thing in this game.
Like, does it serve any other function other than just frustrating people?
It's weird.
Or at least it feels like 90% of the wands are shuffled, you know?
I'm gonna explore just a bit more and then go through.
Fuck!
This doesn't shoot through the chain, apparently.
What do you possess?
Damn!
This guy has a... Okay, sure.
We're not gonna run out of that anytime soon.
Nah, we're at 26 HP.
It's time to stop.
Give me some good perks, please.
What is this?
Circle of unstable metamorphosis.
Hmm.
Oh, man.
I hate these.
Immunity to explosive damage.
Let's try that.
Electric charge.
Um, so we're definitely not doing this anymore.
And this is a non-shuffle wand, but look at the recharge time.
Oh, that's painful.
Painful.
Let's try something new.
What would this look like even?
That's kind of funny.
I like it.
One more.
I see.
Alright, alright, alright.
Pretty neat.
I mean, is the chaos from this gonna cause enough damage?
I'm gonna try this now.
We gotta try something new here in the city.
We can't keep doing shitty stuff.
Um, I guess I like these.
Reduces the spread.
Would be nice to have one of those.
Maybe two of them.
Oh, I don't have some room.
This one.
Where should the last thing I buy be?
Probably some digging.
Or what is this one again?
The fly-downward spell.
I guess we do the digging.
Like,
that is a solid digging wand right there.
Let's leave a couple triggers here.
Now, I'll leave that here.
This wand can go away.
Let's go.
I'm trying something new here.
This will be dangerous.
Cool.
Okay.
I can't go into that.
This is a very unique wand.
I guess the prediction now is that I will kill myself with this.
That's what I will predict here for sure.
Whoa, why?
Oh, the corpses explode.
That's right.
And I'm immune to explosions.
I guess it does extract the gold for me when they explode.
Makes it easy for me to pick up.
Oh, that doesn't destroy environmental stuff, huh?
This wand is not fantastic.
Let me just say that.
But it's cool.
What was that?
Is that a gunner?
A machine gunner?
It's you.
Wait, you don't take any damage?
Okay, there we go.
This is the weirdest wand I've made, I think.
I
just want the non-shuffle wand.
Is that too much to ask for?
It's like just a single non-shuffle wand.
Would be fucking delicious right now.
Dow!
Ah.
Oh, you're a friend.
Come here, friend.
Let's go on adventures.
Okay, this is very good against those.
Don't go in there.
I actually do go in there.
Go in there.
Magic arrow and triggers.
So many triggers.
Again, shuffle wand.
Useless.
Absolutely useless.
I want to get in here.
This is probably really good against bosses if you kite them around and let them walk through the wall.
Pheromone.
Did I kill him?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, I did.
It did.
Nice.
Very good.
There's a spell in there.
Shitty spell, but a spell nonetheless.
What is it?
It's just called bouncing burst.
Yeah.
Bouncing burst.
Is that a frozen fish?
Whoa.
I have to remember, I do have teleport.
But I can't really get out.
Actually, never mind.
What?
Why is it following my friend?
It's a friend, dude.
What?
He can hit me?
I can't hit him?
Whoa.
Thank God you killed him.
He wasn't really my friend.
I think we may just go.
You cannot pass.
Cannot pass.
Yeah, look, they can't pass.
You shut.
It's always these guys.
Fuck me.
I was next to the portal.
Swamp potion.
Bro, I am not getting anywhere.
I also feel like I'm getting some shitty perks.
Oh, look at this dude over here.
What do you want?
Come here.
Oh my God.
He does so much damage.
What is this?
Okay, sure.
Whatever.
Move on.
Next.
I have no idea what's going on.
What the hell is going on here now?
Things are exploding.
I'm gonna make my way up here since I have the ability to do so.
Thank you very much.
I can get up here.
Okay.
It's raining.
See, this is a good start.
At least I get some HP here.
That's what you need.
Slow mana recharge.
Nice.
Beautiful.
Can I get the tablet too?
A couple more shots here.
Damn it.
Also, it sounds like there's a waterfall somewhere, but it's just the rain, I believe.
Got it.
Nice.
What's that?
It's polymorphine.
And no thanks.
You know what?
This is a perfect polymorphine spot.
Pour it in here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fill it up.
And we have a huge body of water right next door.
That's amazing.
See, this is the start you're looking for.
Oh yeah.
Nice.
Let's go.
We have a classic spark bolt and some fire bolts.
But it's very slow though.
One, two.
What's happening here?
Air is filled with fungal spores.
Oh, nice.
That means we get high.
Look at that.
The lantern is embedded in the fungus.
Beautiful in it.
Thanks.
So that also explains why there were so many explosions there.
Whoa.
Gorta almost had me there.
Okay, this is not so good.
That's the way to deal with them.
Big damage.
Uh-oh.
Dangerous terrain here.
Is there anything on that side?
Oh, him is congregation.
I need to... so I need to go say hi to those guys.
With my tablet, that's a guaranteed like 200 golds.
Or thereabouts.
How do I get there?
Do I really go all the way around?
Fine.
Okay, guys.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Beautiful.
Why won't he die?
Quickly grab this, too.
It wasn't quite 200.
But if I hit everyone with the tablet, maybe it could have been.
Very good.
That's a dead end.
Hello.
Come on.
Ah, so close.
It killed something down here, though.
Silver lining.
These hamsters have had, or Gortas have had, way too much caffeine.
This guy is swimming in oil.
Uh-oh.
Okay, that's not bad.
Okay, just stand there, please.
Don't move.
Yes, yes.
Beautiful.
Thank you very much for your cooperation today.
Oh, that looks bad.
Load up.
Oh, fuck!
He went in the lava.
Now, that's a lot of toxic sludge.
Is it just me, or is this hemisphere very quiet?
Oh, no, I need to kill him with this.
460.
Decent amount of money.
It would be incredible if I could find one more heart in here.
Just one more.
Then that's a solid start.
But I can't really bet on it.
It's quite rare.
Pheotic polymorphine.
There's a smell of gas in the air.
That's not good.
I'm playing solid right now.
There's a wand there.
I want it.
Oh, I see.
I see why there's a smell of gas.
A bomb.
Actually, not too bad.
And this gold appeared up here.
I think if there's no room for the gold, it just auto spawns at the first place above him.
Something I've noticed.
Don't hit me.
There's a guy over there that needs a tablet in the face.
But no, no.
Ah, you fucking asshole.
That's annoying, man.
Just because I was a little bit too greedy.
Come on.
Can a man be a little greedy?
So how do I get in there?
I guess I just bomb my way in with my newly found bomb.
Get it.
That's good.
That is the freezing.
In fact, that is a potential steward killer.
It's a tablet combination killer for steward.
That's actually kind of solid right now.
But that also means future stewards are going to pose a problem.
In an ideal world, I will find peace with gods.
I honestly can't see any other way to get a long run other than peace with the gods.
Unless you have a wand that just consistently kills the gods.
Which I almost never have.
And even if I do, then a bigger fucking steward appears and says, what's up, dude?
And then he smacks me over the head.
And it doesn't feel good.
There's bruising, mental scars, as well as physical scars.
Okay, I think I'm done here.
I explored thoroughly, sort of.
Okay, so see here, that's big.
This is act these three.
This is a guaranteed steward killer.
Right there.
There it is.
So lucky.
That's what we need.
Beautiful.
Let's see what's down here.
Concentrated spells.
Oh, now we are talking.
Everything is looking up, guys.
This is really solid.
That one, that one, that one.
This one.
What's this one?
Sea of acid.
Sure.
Maybe that will kill steward.
Sea of acid?
Disk projectile.
Give me this one, that one.
No.
That one.
I'll take these.
So here it is.
This is it.
I'm gonna...
Okay.
Let
me see this.
That's definitely the best.
Use that for this.
And then we're gonna have a long distance cast with that.
How does that seem?
Let me just get rid of that real quick.
Here.
Solid.
But it is shuffled, so that's bad.
Although we actually don't need long distance cast on this.
But it's nice to have.
It is nice to have.
But we don't technically need it.
So, you know, it does actually cause zero mana.
That's cool.
Hold on a minute.
Let me quickly try this sea of acid.
Oh no, hold on.
Acid will eat through brickwork.
So let's be careful here.
This could anger the man.
But so this will also anger the man, I guess.
So I need to be ready in any case here.
Hold on.
Now we gotta put it...
I mean, that is the best.
And we have the tablet ready.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is the steward technique, guys.
Get ready.
This is a home brewed way to kill him.
Okay.
Watch this.
This is how you do it.
You've got to wait for the recharge.
Go in here.
The good news is actually, oh man.
Maybe it is better if we don't kill Stuart.
Because we have a long distance cast.
And if we find a teleport, then we're set.
And we don't have to anger anyone.
You know?
Like, what are the chances of finding a teleport?
There's a chance we never will find one.
Remember that one run?
Where we basically didn't find one until 15 or 20 hours into the run.
Nah, we can't bank on finding one.
That's just a bad strategy.
Because you know the game's gonna fuck me.
When I try to bank on finding something, obviously the game's never gonna give it to me.
That's just how this game works.
It's cruel.
This should be fine, actually.
Let's see here.
Almost.
We're almost there.
Okay, watch.
Beautiful.
And then this is the crucial part.
The tablet.
But wait.
Uh, we gotta anger him first.
Stay mad, bro.
There it goes.
There.
This is the patented Stuart technique.
Slowly but surely he's dying.
You mad, bro?
Are you mad, brother?
Wait, is this costing mana?
Why you only want to do long distance sometimes?
There we go.
Easy like that.
Easy peasy lemon squeezy.
It wasn't easy at all.
Ah, nice.
I'm relieved.
Okay, good, good, good, good.
And now we also have a nice damage here.
Actually, I may put it here instead.
Or there.
I think that's better.
Yep, I like that.
This one can be here.
Although, should I be keeping this?
I guess it's not the worst.
This is number one.
And I think I am good.
Imagine if I actually find a teleport in the next holy mountain.
I would be so fucking pissed.
I think I'm gonna take some vision as well.
Or should I?
Maybe I'll let go.
I don't need the circle of stillness right now.
I have this.
The chain bolt is more than enough for what I'm about to encounter.
And then we need to dig.
Oops.
Which one was the digging?
That one?
It was.
Let's go.
Come on.
Okay.
Almost there.
And this is our home base now.
This is HQ.
This is where we're gonna hang out and do things.
Cool things.
Okay, so that's perfect.
These things can go to hell.
I do kind of want to try this again.
Man, it costs so much mana.
Some is a large body of acid below the caster.
How large?
Damn.
Yo, I wonder how effective that is against bosses.
That's a lot of acid.
Well, I should have done that to get out and not just make a little shitty hole.
Also put the this one back, please.
I should have taken... You know what?
I'm gonna take my digging thing with me.
Do I have any other digging capabilities other than that?
Because I don't like it very much.
Not really.
All right, fine.
But it's gonna suck so much.
Better than nothing, I guess.
And we can always come back and change it.
That's a good thing about having an HQ.
That's all a man needs.
Just a bit more.
There we go.
A bunch of bombs.
Yeah, it's better than that.
I'll take it for sure.
Cool.
And that's right, we have this as well.
Let's not forget that.
So we're gonna be sustaining here.
And you know what?
This is the perfect setup to go into fungal caverns as well.
Because there's so many wands there and we're gonna heal with them.
So I may as well just do that first.
You know, I think it's a great idea.
And we have the tablet.
Let's not forget that.
We can probably use that in there.
If shit hits the fan.
The only thing is I kind of hate my primary wand here.
Let's see here.
It's very slow because it adds lots of cast delay.
So if I put it on something like this one instead, it's gonna be much better.
I think I'm just gonna do that right now.
It also has much more mana charge speed and all that.
Let's just prepare as much.
I just love having an HQ.
The fact that I can do this now, it's big.
I did kind of ruin it though with the acid.
But that's fine.
I don't really care about these.
Much better, much better, much better.
Get rid of that crap.
Maybe I'll bring this with me.
Maybe I'll put that on the same thing.
Just to save some space here.
I can use it in emergencies.
I just don't want to throw away too many wands.
Nice.
Extra max health.
Sweet.
And a wand.
All right, a good start here.
Not bad.
It's better than this one, I think.
Yeah.
For sure.
Off to fungal caverns.
And heal a little bit.
Oh, here we go.
Nice.
Yep, we're getting that.
Definitely.
Let's keep going left.
I'm tempted to go back already just to put on the reduced reach out of time.
I think I should.
Actually, I do like having one more of these maybe.
No, I have one already.
If I suddenly find myself with lots of riches, there's something to consider.
I'm gonna make my damage one a little better.
Let's just equip ourselves the most for fungal caverns.
I am deathly afraid of that place, okay?
Don't judge me.
It has killed me numerous times.
You've got to prepare.
And part of that preparation is sipping the beer.
All right, so here we go.
Amazing.
Much better.
And you can take that.
You can even put a light on it because that would be kind of cool.
Is there anything else I should be doing?
How does this work with that?
That's better, right?
Where's the one I had before that was decent at that?
Hmm.
I don't have a... Wait, what's... Whoa!
What?
The fuck is that?
Why is there a frozen acid?
Huh?
Weird.
All right.
Okay, 299 gold.
Straight to fungal caverns now.
Now we have a great wand.
I'm feeling great about this run here.
This is a solid start so far.
I just need to really play it slow.
Keep myself topped up.
And don't do anything rash.
That's what I need to do.
I am missing a dedicated digging wand.
Something that is actually good and not something like this.
Whoa!
Lava.
They're teasing me
through the wood.
Am I really gonna...
Also, by the way, last time I was down here there was a chest buried.
I want to see if that's the same thing now.
Ha ha ha!
What did I fucking say?
I'm a goddamn oracle.
You know how I know that?
Every time there's this area, so the game is made up of these tiles.
There's always a chest here.
Do I want that?
No, that sucks.
Don't even want it.
God damn it.
Okay, the portal is there.
Wait, go around.
I want to get to the wand first.
I guess we'll go through here.
Unless I can save time.
Nah, that's actually... that takes more time.
But maybe going around and then down.
Nah, I'm just gonna dig here.
Let's just dig here.
It sucks, but it is what it is.
Just dig it up.
All right, it doesn't take that long, actually.
I need energy orb.
That's my favorite.
Nope, that's a horrible wand.
Very horrible.
Okay, so I can't go any more left there.
How do I get to fungal caverns?
Probably keep going up.
I just feel like I already explored that.
God damn it.
Also, you know what?
I'm just gonna go back and heal.
I was trying to destroy that mine earlier.
Isn't that kind of ironic?
And I didn't want to bother with it because it's so hard to hit with this wand I have here.
There we go.
That's how powerful wand experimenter is.
Just like that.
Full HP.
Let's go up here now and then left.
There's a guy in there.
Okay, I have to dig here, apparently.
I can't get through.
The level is just locked off.
It's insanely annoying, but not much you can do.
I'm just trying to get to the promised land here.
Actually, let me try and have a look.
Wait, what?
Oh, the hole here.
Was that there before?
I don't know if it was.
I feel like something exploded.
Invasiblium.
We made it.
Yes.
Time to rock.
Everyone's world.
It's gonna be one hell of a show.
You know what?
Piece of shit.
Get shot through the wall.
Worm pheromone.
No, thanks for Serkum.
Yes, thanks.
Drink some of that.
What the fuck is that?
Don't hit me with those things, please.
But Serkum is going to come in handy here.
Flammoxium.
And we got to get high, of course.
Don't hit me.
Scary.
Just exploded.
How does this work when I'm preserved?
It doesn't even affect it.
Oh, I was scratching my nose.
Immediately, this guy shows up and teleports away.
Did he go down here?
Ambrosia.
Oh wait, you don't drink that.
You pour it.
I don't want it.
Yeah, pour it on me.
Give me Ambrosia.
It's a very unwieldy potion.
I wish I could drink it.
I hate having to pour it on myself.
It's honestly one of the primary reasons I also don't like Invisiblium very much.
It's just unwieldy.
I have to do that every time.
How am I gonna get this thing destroyed?
Okay, there it goes.
Water.
Whoa.
That's more Invisiblium.
Got a wand.
Now we can heal with that.
Uh, no, keep this wand.
But, yeah, yeah, keep it.
Keep it.
Honey.
I gotta find a big collection of fungus and then I'm gonna go to town.
It's gonna be a feast.
Home bringer.
No, but I will do this.
Oh, look.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's the Berserkium that makes the freezing bigger.
Look.
Oh, wait, was I affected by Berserkium?
I'm not actually sure.
Wait, what is this thing?
Oh, it looked like a blue pouch that I could pick up.
Not what it is, though.
I want to get in there.
Can I get in there?
I can.
In fact, I can go from the top.
That's the good thing about having the luminous drill.
It can't go through everything.
It's just slow until you figure out to make it non-slow.
Pollen.
I mean, that is gonna upgrade this one if I can put the luminous drill on it.
And I can if I want to go back and do all that.
I'm lazy.
I'm very lazy.
I think I will do it, but I will do it on my way back.
Not right now.
Just in case there's a better wand.
Who knows?
Would be amazing to go there and change it up, come back here, and then find the immediately better wand, you know?
What do we got here?
Actually, a decent wand.
Even better than the one we just found.
I will take this.
That's a straight up better wand.
Nice.
Very good, very good.
And money situation is also looking grand.
I do see a bunch of mushrooms.
Let's go to town.
Eat, eat, eat, eat, eat.
Oh yeah, eat it all.
So good.
Let's see what happens.
Worm blood,
worm blood.
So worm blood changed into something.
I wonder what.
I guess we'll find out at some point.
More berserkium.
Hey, that's big.
Gimme.
Yes.
Love berserkium.
I've become a huge fan of the berserkium lately.
Okay, there's just one over there.
I gotta find a teleport.
That would make everything right now.
Given the long distance cast.
Unfortunately, we already did anger the gods.
And we have to remember, as soon as we step into the holy mountain, the guy's gonna be angry at us.
So we gotta prepare.
Did everything die here?
Mostly.
Nice.
Lightning bolts.
Now that is actually great, I think.
I think that can kill Stuart.
Imagine long distance cast together with this.
Not too bad, huh?
Hold on.
Just reveal a bit.
Now this one is great.
Do I let go of the luminous?
No, I don't.
No, no, no, I need that.
So I can get out of the mountains.
Okay, I'm gonna go back and put luminous drill on this, and then come back and grab this.
This is too important.
We gotta do this now.
The easiest way out would probably be to just make a hole here.
Just so we have an easy way back.
Unless we can quickly get around here.
That's probably fine.
Come on, get rid of the pixels.
Ah, what?
There's this pixel right there.
I can't get rid of it.
There we go.
It's a bit of RNG, like where the visual happens is not actually where it happens in the game, it seems.
Worm pheromone.
I do wonder what worm blood became.
I guess I must have revealed that just now.
Sick stuff.
Very good.
In fact, I'm gonna keep revealing on the way back.
Oh no, I ran out.
No, I didn't.
Where's the reveal?
Oh, it's shuffle, of course.
Yeah, yeah, that makes sense.
Make a little bit of a shortcut here.
We go around that.
Here's everybody.
Oh yeah.
Man, this weekend has been gaming for me.
The entire weekend.
It's the best thing ever.
I hope you're also having a great weekend.
Or what's left of it, I guess.
Okay, here we go.
Now I want to put this on this one instead.
What is that?
The acid trail.
Acid trail.
You know what?
I'll keep it.
We gotta try new things.
Maybe we'll do massive acid build at some point.
But all I need is the unlimited spells, I guess, because otherwise this is kind of useless.
Or we go up and we murder Yalgamisti.
That's another path to that success.
Biterium.
Get rid of these.
Now put this here.
It's better and we make up another slot here for another wand.
Although, can we somehow combine some of these a little bit?
It doesn't seem so.
Triple kit bolts.
Could be a decent digger here.
Whoa!
I guess that makes sense, given the stats.
We just need some mana for that.
Yeah.
Nice.
Let me also quickly check this.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
We just don't have the mana.
Put this up here.
It's better than we had before and that's all I ask, so I'm happy.
Now we can replace that wand with the one we want.
I may actually just refresh my spells here too.
I still have more vision.
And I never take these, so I may as well start using them a little bit.
You know?
I'm not using it enough, I don't think.
I think I on average die when I have all of them up and not even a single one used.
The only ones I take are the ones where I accidentally get them because Stuart pushes me into them.
Don't be so stingy.
Just do it, you know?
Okay.
Now we go pick up the amazing wand and we're gonna get high again.
Probably enough time has passed now.
That's the Giga Disc projectile.
You know what?
I will actually buy it because that could be something nice against Stuart on a long distance cast maybe.
Make it pass through his shield.
I'm also thinking long distance cast Sea of Acid.
See how well that does.
That way I can be at a safe distance and just go, or I could wait for him right above him.
I know where he spawns, right?
Wait, how do I?
Hold on, let me change these.
I could wait for him where he spawns and stay right above him and then just see if Acid him in the face.
That wouldn't be too bad.
But it is risky because if it doesn't work, then I'm in a bad spot.
Okay, where's that shortcut in here?
It was actually all the way at the top.
This way.
Wait, where did I?
Was it over here?
Oh no, I never did make the little hole.
I went around.
Shit, man.
I remember thinking of making a hole, but then I changed my mind.
I went back around.
Oh my god.
Well, since we're here, I'm gonna get high.
Eat all this.
Just do it.
Oh yeah, delicious.
Delicious stuff.
Oh, there's so much over here too.
I'm gonna grab that.
Uh-oh.
Don't you acid this place?
No!
Fucking assholes.
Contaminated my crime scene.
This should be enough.
200 seconds?
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
It's happening.
Steam!
Uh-oh.
I wonder what that means.
Okay, let's go grab it.
Uh, yes.
I'm gonna kill this guy through the wall, because that's just how I be.
I'd be like that.
No, I can't.
Okay, fine.
That's unstable teleport.
What's that?
Flammoxium.
See, I don't want to destroy that flammoxium.
I may not have a choice.
Yeah, fuck.
Ah!
This is just insane.
Like, you see the issue coming up and you're powerless, because it just somehow always happens.
We got to find a wand right now so we can heal up.
That's the thing about these perks.
That's so important.
You know, vampirism and wand experimenter, they allow for fuck-ups, which is something I sorely need.
Oops.
Water me, water me.
No, wait!
Did all water get into steam?
What's happening?
Please no.
I really hope that's not the case.
Can we get a polymorphine into water or something, please?
That would be fan-fucking-tastic.
Sincerely, me.
Uh, wait, did I just get a graphical glitch?
Hey, the balloon went up!
What's up, man?
Oh!
Interesting stuff.
Ugh!
I mean, sure.
It's to heal.
I can also heal with the lightning, by the way.
Let's do that first.
Just use it up and
that should be it.
Yeah, this one.
Oh!
What?
Wow!
Okay, yeah.
So we gotta... we gotta rise while doing it.
What a wand.
That's what it takes to be a wand experimenter.
You gotta be able to test drive these things, you know?
You gotta have the balls for it.
Not everyone can do it, you know?
You gotta be born for that sort of thing.
Give me this.
There's actually a wand here, too.
Let me quickly see what that is.
No thanks.
Unstable teleportation.
I have no water on me.
A death cross!
How about we don't do that?
Forget my speech about having balls and all that.
I don't have any right now.
They have shriveled up and escaped into a different dimension.
Nowhere to be seen again.
Acceleration.
I will drink a bit of this and kill him.
With that!
Oh!
Okay, well he died, so I guess it worked.
Now we just gotta experiment a little bit more with some wands here.
I don't want to do it with the death cross, though.
No way I'm that crazy.
No way, Jose.
I see potions here.
What's that?
Fire potion?
No.
Concentrated mana?
Oh!
A chest!
Let me check it out.
I'm trying not to hit the chest just yet, in case there's money in there.
And I can't get to it in time.
Okay, this is a bit dangerous.
Maybe I'll do it now.
Do it.
Hey!
Okay.
Don't take it yet.
More wands, please.
Also, I'm gonna get high again in a moment here.
Did water actually get transformed?
Because I haven't seen any water in forever.
I really hope not.
That would ruin my day.
And when I say day, it would ruin the next 30 minutes, probably.
Because then I'll probably be dead.
I can't even get out of here.
I gotta go up this way.
Copper pouch.
Go here.
Now you!
You get to die.
Okay, let's try and get high again.
Careful not to eat the toxic stuff.
That should be enough.
Let's see if there's been enough time.
Oh, copper!
Let's go check the pouch.
There's copper in that.
Oh, pouchy!
Little pouchy.
Are you working on your abs?
Little naz?
Pea soup!
Pea- Wait, is that the thing I can eat?
Wait!
No way.
No way!
Wait, what?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Lots of pea soup here.
I'll take this and fill it up.
Now drink.
No, it doesn't heal me.
But it does make me satiated, I guess.
I'm gassy!
You're feeling pressure inside.
That's not good.
Uh-oh, we're gonna fart a lot.
I guess I'll keep the pouch for now.
Oh look, I'm smelly!
Okay, that's kinda neat.
Did I ever fire this wand?
I'm gonna- Ah, that's too dangerous though, isn't it?
It's too dangerous.
There's no way that's a good idea, but hold on, there was also one down here.
That's the one I need.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, that's the one, that's the one.
This one should be safe.
Oh yeah, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
Okay, now we switch back.
Don't touch that.
It's hard not to touch it when you have the extra- Oh wait, that's not the right one.
Or somewhere over here.
Oh look, this is actually the spot, this is the spot.
We need the...
We need the demon eye now.
Book of guidance.
Yep.
And you know what else?
It's an upside down triangle.
Maybe it could also indicate blood.
Who knows?
Where did I put my- Oh, it's here.
That's the one.
Thank you.
I'm gonna go here.
Blood is still blood.
That's good.
I think I'm done in this place.
I think we have really explored the fungal caverns here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
We're fine, we're fine.
You know what?
I think I'm gonna bring some fungus with me.
Just if we need to get high on the road, you know?
If we need to take a pit stop at some point and just calm down.
Have a bit of fun.
It would be nice to have a bag of weed, you know?
Gotta find a good amount of it up there, I see some.
I'm gonna scoop that up.
Oh yeah, come with me.
We're gonna get high later.
It's gotta be good.
We're gonna find a nice little spot with a good view.
And just really...
...inhale those shrooms.
I'm gonna watch the sunset.
Actually, let's take shrooms when we get to the surface.
You know, we can watch the sun...
...and get high.
Okay.
Let's find some wands so we can heal ourselves.
And start using the all-seeing eye here to find the wands.
I need to mouse over things because they will tell me if it's been transformed.
I don't remember if I ever shot that.
Don't think I did.
It would be nice to have another one of these, I guess.
No, I'm gonna leave it.
I do have one already.
Light it up.
Oh, look at that, look at that.
A shiny orb.
Just for me.
One more?
Yeah, we're fine.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Wait, what was over here?
Oh yeah, right, the wand.
I believe I shot this a couple times, but I still have more shots on it.
Yeah.
Heal me up before I go, go.
Yeah,
more healing.
Whoopity-whoop.
Nice.
Awesome sauce.
Full HP.
If I can find a teleport now, I am golden.
Much like that shiny orb.
So, you see this?
This is the same thing we saw just before.
There's a chest down there.
100% though, friendo.
Watch this.
What do you want to bet?
It's gonna be a bit annoying to get in there.
Oh, actually, we made it.
Quite quickly.
Come on, show yourself.
Don't make me look bad.
Okay.
I swear, most of the time, there's something in there.
I think I'm just unlucky.
I'm gonna go around here.
I gotta look for... So, something... I guess...
Something else has turned into blood.
It's even the small one!
Fan-fucking-tastic!
Oh my god!
That's huge!
I'm gonna come back for the lightning.
Wait a minute.
Let me kill you first.
I'm gonna kill some of these.
Now that's what I'm talking about!
Oh, right.
It's a little bit random right now.
Can't believe it was right here!
Okay, so I'm just going up, up, up, up, up.
A little to the left and down.
Next to these two hanging nuclear thingies.
Okay.
So, what we're gonna do is this.
Watch.
We're gonna put...
This is actually perfect, because it also has heavy spread.
We're gonna put that on...
Oh no, wait, heavy spread is shit with the luminous drill.
Unless we put a dummy on it.
Do we have a dummy?
Hmm.
Get rid of these.
And...
I don't even know.
Get rid of that one.
Let's think.
Can I make this work somehow?
With the luminous drill?
Also, it's just gonna be too fast.
Yeah, I'm not... I don't even have the mana for that.
So it's actually not gonna work.
We're gonna leave it like that for now.
And then we're gonna put a long distance on this.
Because now we are so cold.
Oh my god.
Fantastic.
Kinda wanna get rid of the luminous drill now that we can go through walls.
Most walls, that is.
And instead, I'm gonna put this one here.
So I can do a little bit of digging in soft materials.
And I'm not afraid to throw this away either, just because we have another one.
But this is such a good wand.
Maybe I'll put it on...
This one in...
Also, hold on.
Is it better to...
Oh, we gotta throw our shit on this.
This is now the main.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Much better, much better, much better, much better.
And then we can throw this wand away, because it's shuffled, nobody likes it.
Boo!
Right?
This one is probably even better there.
We can throw this one away.
That means that's a little too slow, so that's not okay.
Very good.
We are rolling.
Nothing else to be done.
Good.
Let's go.
And look at that.
Wait!
Steam transformed.
Large firebolt.
This is already a much better wand than this.
Do I actually replace this one?
Don't shoot it yet.
We need it for healing.
Oh!
And so many shotgun people.
Triple scatter?
No, thanks.
What do we got here?
A triple spell.
Ooh, minus cast delay.
But it is a shuffle.
So that sucks.
What are these little particles in the steam?
Look, there is confetti in the steam.
Something is going on.
That's not normal steam.
Why is there confetti in there?
Oh my God!
I'm an idiot.
We got to go back.
I put it on the wrong wand.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait, that's too far.
Left, left, left, left.
Please.
Okay, there it is.
Fuck, we only have...
What?!
How do we only have shuffle?
Didn't I have an extra wand here?
Hello?
Alright, well...
It is what it is.
For now.
It also seems to be...
That's okay, it's okay.
Oh, wait, wait.
We got to put it on this one.
Yep.
That's the one.
That is the one.
There, there, throw this away.
Boo!
Better.
Much better.
Confetti everywhere.
Like, what has been...
It's got to be water.
I haven't seen water in forever.
Water has been transformed to steam.
Yeah.
Which is very unfortunate, because I can't...
let go of stains on me.
And I'm going to take so much damage because of it.
Like, stop!
Get it off of me!
There we go.
But that is the risk you run when you get high.
Although, we could just keep getting high.
And hope that it changes back.
Is that even possible?
I wonder.
Look at this huge pile of coal in there!
If I had a better digging wand, I would have totally gone in there and cleaned it up to see if something was hiding in there.
Almost there's got to be, right?
With that amount?
Too suspicious.
Look at this weird configuration.
Kill them all.
I've spent a lot of time in the coal pits.
Hello!
Special man.
Nothing exciting.
I think it's time we just leave.
But, hold on.
Stewart's going to be waiting, so...
We've got to find a wand and quickly heal up.
I don't remember if I used this one.
I didn't.
That was easy.
Where did my wand go?
Oh, I didn't have a wand here before.
Give me that one instead, because it has the triple on it.
And I would like to have that.
Now we go.
Okay, so the way we're going to deal with...
Let's think.
Let's just run this through.
We have circle of stillness.
And...
We do have this.
But maybe I'll quickly change it so that my long distance...
throws a...
Giga Disc projectile.
I'm going to have these ready.
I'm going to try different options here on the fly.
It has to be...
Or maybe I find a way to quickly dig myself into a hole again and leave my tablet between him and me.
So I can think about it.
Because I can always sit there in long distance cast as much as I want.
That could be an option, so maybe a luminous drill.
If we quickly need to make a little hole...
Worst case, I can always get out...
and come back.
Yes, that seems good.
I can always just leave, because I have long distance cast on teleport.
I kind of want to try the Sea of Acid on a long distance.
I've got to prepare one wand.
This could be the wand I prepare.
I'm going to throw these away.
Throw that away.
I can always pick it up later.
No, this is shuffle.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
No, no, no.
Abort, abort.
This is actually... This shoots quite fast.
This may just be a way to kill him.
Because this goes through his shield.
Go.
I think I'm just going to keep it simple here.
Keep it simple.
Yeah, look.
Water's gone.
Black hole!
Very nice.
There he is.
Look at that menacing eye right there.
Actually, it's not an eye.
It's the little light at the top of his staff.
So, I'm going to change my... I'm going to start digging a little bit here.
Or do I just kill him?
Uh, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig.
Nah, fuck, he's coming.
He's coming, he's coming, he's coming.
Yeah, okay, fuck it, fuck it.
Hey!
Mana.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Got him!
Yes!
I'm going to take this.
Sweet!
All right, very nice.
That's big.
Uh, put it...
down here.
Nobody wants to see you.
Now that...
is cool.
Black holes, very neat.
Okay, let's see what we got here.
Freeze fields, contact damage.
No, I don't like any of these.
Eh...
Ah!
That could be nice.
To transport things around, you know, it is a transporter ability.
Also, by the way, by the way, I want to try something here while I'm here.
This is it.
I'm going to use...
That's the only one that can do it.
I want to test something here.
So watch this.
Just dislodge this thing.
More.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
Ah!
What's happening, what's happening, what's happening?
Oh, my teleport one is all fucked.
I see, I see, I see, I see.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Don't hit me, don't hit me, don't...
Fuck!
Go!
Okay, okay, okay.
We don't have any water.
Come on, get it off me.
Get it off me, get it off of me.
Good.
Now...
Put this back here, put this up here.
Can I really not use any?
That's unreal.
We gotta find a bit of want.
No.
Eh?
That one.
Cost 180.
I mean, it's shuffle.
I'd rather have this one then.
No, because it doesn't have enough mana.
Fuck!
Fine!
I'll buy this one.
Put these here.
Was it that one?
Or was this one?
Yeah, put it back.
And then on this one, we're gonna put the black hole.
All the black holes, in fact.
This is the black hole want now.
So listen.
What happened last time?
Is that...
I, um...
So I accidentally let this one fall somewhere.
Like here, right?
And then I went on to another holy mountain.
And I...
Rerolled a perk there.
Then I came back here and the price didn't increase.
Okay?
So that's the test we're gonna perform now.
I will not take any of these.
I will go to the next holy mountain.
I will re-rule, if I need to.
And then I'll come back here later and see if it actually works.
It seems like a bit of a bug, but...
I need to confirm.
Because that was like, as soon as I saw that, my mind was like, oh shit, we can abuse this, you know?
Okay.
Are we good?
I feel like my damage wand is kind of mediocre at this point.
Like it could be better.
But I'm not really...
I don't have the fucking skill to create something good here.
I just don't.
We have the digging, we have this.
It's fine, I guess.
Actually, I'm never using this.
Let's put that away.
Maybe later I'll use it.
Okay.
We gotta go find some wands and experiment with them.
And then we gotta kill this dude.
Oh, look at this here.
What's happening here?
I guess someone made an Eldritch Portal and died.
Silly goose.
Why would you do that?
Oh, look at this here now.
Oh ho ho ho.
Well, well, well.
Essence to power.
That's really good.
But also expensive in terms of mana.
Wait.
He just bled lava.
Freezing liquid has become lava?
Did that just happen?
Is that what I just witnessed?
Kill them all.
With minimal scratches.
That's very unheard of for me.
We get to heal here now, though.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Just beautiful.
Do it.
Yeah, look at this.
Lava transformed.
It's got to be a steam transform man.
I'm not done transforming.
We are getting high right now.
We shall transform the world into a more non-hostile place.
Do it.
Let's see it.
Acid.
Oh, no, that can be... that is...
That could be really bad, guys.
Uh-oh.
It's Sea of Acid time.
Do we dare to try Sea of Acid?
Oh, shit.
There's a dude over here.
Oh, nice.
He died kind of quick.
Okay, let's be careful here.
Wait, wait.
I need to... no, hold on.
Hey!
That's big!
That's amazing!
No more acids!
Whoa!
Oh, yeah, baby!
Okay, cheers to that.
Ah, that feels amazing.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Back we go to the teleport.
Uh, uh, uh, wait a minute.
Should I maybe try this?
Let's see how much mana.
It is a lot of mana.
But how much more damage will it do?
We gotta... we gotta test.
I have a feeling maybe it can be good.
I shoot much slower, but we'll have to see how much more damage it adds.
Okay, so there's still blood just like that.
Like normal blood is still normal blood.
Okay.
Go here now.
I can't.
Did I just make a hole in the snow?
I guess the teleport is a bit aggressive, right?
It also did break the glass at one point, remember?
And then we died because of it.
Unfortunately, the... freezing vapor...
Oh!
Is that why there's confetti?
The freezing liquid, right, has become lava.
But it still gives off a bit of freezing vapor, and maybe that is being immediately transformed to steam.
Or something.
Oh shit, man, okay.
I'm not so sure about the, uh, new wand I made.
Let's see.
Thirty-three... like that didn't... really do anything.
But dude, it's kind of big that there's no freezing vapor.
That is such an annoying thing.
And now it's not annoying at all.
But I don't like my new wand.
I'm gonna change it back.
Get rid of this one.
This is much better like this.
Oh, what happened there?
Bubble spark with trigger?
No.
No, thanks.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Now I just want to transform the, uh, toxic into...
I don't even know.
That would be great.
Toxic into water, please.
You know what?
We're gonna do it.
We're gonna transform toxic into water right now.
Uh, I still have some stuff left.
Let's get high again.
Hopefully enough time has passed.
Do it.
Do it!
Let's see what happens.
I'm scared.
I'm taking gambles here doing this.
Okay!
Let's go check it out.
I saw some blood somewhere over here.
Ouch.
I'm actually proud of myself.
That was a good fight.
Okay, so hold on.
These guys bleed.
What do they bleed?
Seema?
The hell is Seema?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can I destroy this corpse?
Look, the blood appears and then disappears.
The fuck is Seema?
Am I supposed to know what Seema is?
I don't know what Seema is.
English is not my first language.
Maybe it's something common.
I don't know.
Uh, whatever.
Well, it's, um, no more blood, I guess.
We have Seema now.
They Seema rolling.
They hate him.
Octagonal bolt bundle.
Eh, I don't know about that one, bro.
I'm gonna pass that up.
No thanks.
I'm very worried about the lava.
Like, like, exactly.
Look at that shit.
Those things have suddenly become...
D-E-A-N-jurus.
Duh, don't fall in the portal.
We gotta heal first because we also have a steward coming.
What the fuck was that up there?
Did you see that?
There were three flaming barrels.
Peplicate spell.
What is that?
Cast five copies of a projectile in a pentagonal pattern.
But the copies still cost mana.
Er...
Okay.
Alright.
You know what this sounds like when you shoot the chain bolt so fast?
Sounds like a...
scuffed version of a Star Wars laser.
Oh, burning!
Seema!
Seema, Seema, Seema!
Seema.
Where are the Wands at?
I need healing!
Must experiment!
I gotta be careful... I can die!
If I'm not careful here... If I'm not careful... I'm actually almost dead!
We gotta go, we gotta go, we gotta go!
That's it!
We're leaving… Right now!
Take no ch- Oh, shit, he's here, he's here, he's here, he's here!
Quickly check out the wands, quickly check out the wands, quick quick quick quick quick.
Yes!
Quick.
Oh I have no more money.
There was an ad man on that one.
Shit.
Oh no no no no no no no no.
Wait I can't get through him.
Run!
What do we have?
More blood?
Oh dude watch this.
Peek-a-boo!
Wait what?
What's happening?
I can't shoot.
Go here we go.
There's it!
Oh they're enraged now huh?
Too fucking bad bro.
Too fucking brat bro.
Brat brat brat brat sucks.
Did you know that?
Now I have money for this.
I'm gonna... actually energy orb is also super nice here.
Energy orb.
Let's put this here.
Let's put this there.
And now I'm gonna...
take that, grab this bad boy.
Not that we need the mana I guess.
But you know.
Aotic path.
Let's leave that here as well.
Get rid of that wand.
Now with what I've got, there's got to be something good I can make.
There's just... there's gotta be.
There's gotta be.
I don't have a lot of options like it.
I don't have a trigger.
But this is already quite good I guess.
It's not fantastic.
I think that's better.
Just straight up.
What if I didn't do this?
Oh wow.
The castelae added from this one is really affecting it.
Can we circumvent that?
Oh maybe we can.
Hold up now.
Kinda.
We need a dummy spell.
Like that for example.
Or just throw that in there.
Oh but then it won't affect the...
Not bad.
Let's put this one...
There it is!
By the way I wasn't just randomly rearranging.
I actually thought it made sense because the reduced recharge time was being wasted on this guy.
And we know that the stat changes on this.
The recharge time reduction and castelae reduction only works to the next slot.
It doesn't go throughout the entire thing.
So now I actually put this on this guy.
So this one is gonna add castelae but this one removes it.
So does that.
At least I like to think I understood that just now.
Maybe I didn't.
Who knows.
So here's the test.
Here is the test.
We are gonna... In fact I may as well try this again here.
Why do this?
He has a wand!
What is that wand?
That's a scary wand.
Let me take that.
You can't play with that down here.
That's just no bueno.
No bueno.
Wait a minute.
What are stats on this?
Stats are not bad.
3.31.03.
Oh but it's not enough slots.
Not enough slots.
I'm even thinking if we get rid of this and put in that.
I don't care about the luminous drill having a weird direction.
Is that faster?
It's about the same.
But you know what dude?
Double.
Yep.
Now let's see if we can't double dip on the mana.
Double dipping the mana.
Let's see.
Get rid of that one.
Hold on.
There's no double dip there.
One.
Two.
So one.
Why is that not doubling?
What if I do this?
I'm just trying to test here.
Nah, honestly this whole shit is a mystery to me.
I feel like there's so much shit happening under the hood that it's not explained here.
That it's just... it doesn't make too much sense to me at least.
It's just trial and error for me.
I'm doomed to trial and error this forever.
Double spell.
I mean this obviously is the one that reduces recharge time.
Now that's nice but I gotta double dip on the add mana.
How
do I do that?
So it's gonna do add mana.
We do a double spell.
The add mana is being used on...
Wait a second.
What if we modify this?
Just as a test.
Weird.
Oh wait, I guess castelay is the issue here.
It's not actually recharge time.
No, it's not.
No wait, 0.03?
This also reduces castelay.
I need to understand this man.
I'm actually losing my mind.
I've been losing my mind over this shit since starting this game.
So we are limited by recharge right now and you can see it because of the bar.
It's recharging up there.
And that is because we do an add mana.
We do a double spell.
This is a modifier, modifier...
So there's another spell to be used but it's not there so it's gonna go to the front.
Right?
So we need a dummy there.
Is that the double dip?
Ah!
There it is!
Motherfucker!
Now the reason why it didn't work before is because look...
Add mana.
Double spell.
This is one spell.
It's looking for another spell.
This is not another spell, it's a modifier.
So if I do this, we give, we satisfy it now.
We give it the spell.
There it is.
You happy bitch?
I'm talking to the game here.
I'm talking to this luminous drill.
We got our wand.
Ladies and gentlemen, the weekend.
Fuckin' hell.
Alright.
Now.
I'm gonna try and click on this thing.
Wait a minute, I didn't like any of the perks, right?
Did I like this perk?
I don't like that perk.
I don't like these perks.
Okay.
Click on it!
Oh, I don't have enough gold.
Let's go find some gold.
It's gold time.
Thanks.
I gotta pick up some of this gold.
SEMA.
Ah!
Very nice.
Look at all this SEMA appearing out of nowhere.
I wonder if SEMA will put out fires.
I'm gonna pick some of this SEMA up.
Let's, let's try.
Okay.
I'm not so sure.
Does it transform the toxic shit?
No, it lays at the bottom.
I'm gonna go right instead.
Also, look at the, uh...
confetti.
There's confetti coming off of the SEMA.
It's the SEMA making the confetti.
I guess?
The confetti is a mystery to me.
Oh wait, freezing vapor isn't being turned into what I thought it was, unless we changed it back somehow.
I think I was wrong regarding the freezing vapor earlier.
Yeah.
Finally.
Okay, it's healing time.
And it's not even a bad wand.
It does feel good to have a machine gun back.
MG42 is back in action, baby.
Whoops, that was a bit risky.
That was a bit risky.
I realized my mistake a millisecond before I did it.
What is that weird, uh...
graphical effect at the end of the...
Oh, maybe it's always been there.
The triplicate bolt.
So much SEMA.
I'm gonna google what SEMA is.
I need to see what that is.
SEMA.
SEMA is a Finnish fermented low-level alcoholic drink and soft drink.
Of course it would be Finnish.
That makes a lot of damn sense.
I was about to say it kind of looked like whiskey.
Okay, and I was like, let's try and put out fires with it.
Yeah, that's gonna work.
That's a friendo.
Unfortunately, I don't care about it.
It's so sad, isn't it?
Okay, I have the money.
Now watch this.
800.
So it says from now on, I want... okay, this is... we're double testing now.
Take that perk.
Now we go up.
That way.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Oh, don't go in the fire.
What's up, guys?
I'm back with a better wand.
You like it?
I need some speed on this wand.
Oh, we could get high again.
I don't think there's enough here.
I can make it enough.
We're getting high again.
Yes!
Eat it all!
Let's go.
Show me.
Oh, yeah.
Have you ever seen someone get high this many times?
Vomit!
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Did my mushroom get turned into vomit?
I cannot get high anymore.
That's it?
No more high?
Oh, what?
400!
Guys!
Okay.
Wait.
Hold on, we need money.
400.
400, baby!
Uh, wait a minute.
Wait, SEMA counts as water?
Dude, we are... we uh...
Did I just discover a way to always be able to... well, not always, but almost always be able to re-roll?
Oh, fuck me.
These guys are the scariest.
Just make it rain.
Teleporting in here is a little bit sketchy.
Unless I teleport in there and shoot from in there.
Watch this.
Oh, hold on.
Yes!
The strategy.
Okay.
Is that gonna... let's try and heal with it.
All right, that's not too bad.
Hey, not bad at all.
Neat.
Some healing there.
Very cool.
I need 400.
My question now is...
I can...
So, the fact that every time you re-roll, the price doubles.
You know, that very quickly tends towards infinity, you know?
Like, you don't need a lot of iterations there to make it completely unpayable.
Like, you will not have enough money.
If you can reduce that by even three or four times, or how many times you can do this now?
That's a big deal.
In the long run.
I need more wants.
And money.
Don't shoot that at me.
Ow, ow, ow.
Shotgun man.
Hey!
Easiest healing in my life.
Also, I forgot to bring my last wand I had.
Shit.
My vision wand.
It's lost.
What do I have in here?
Ambrosia?
That's right.
Ambrosia.
Oh no, it's this guy.
Oh well, he died.
So, I have 400.
Let's, let's, uh, go re-roll.
Got him.
I want to find unlimited spells.
Really bad.
Ah, may as well go heal now.
What do you got there?
Oh, haha.
Not very scary, is it?
And let me go!
Now, that's a lot of, uh, steam.
Man, where's the entrance?
Is it over here?
It's gotta be here.
What is also up here?
Ah, nothing.
Here we go, here we go.
Ahhh!
Sixteen...
Wait a minute.
Okay, so the way you would do this, I guess...
You would have to go around and displace all of these...
I don't even know what to call these.
The perk re-roll.
Before you take any of them.
Because that way...
If you take the first, they're all gonna be, okay.
So, let's say you find a black hole in the beginning of the game.
Right?
You find it in the hemisphere.
And you don't take any of the perks, it's a little bit crazy.
It's a crazy strategy.
But you don't take any perks.
Unless it's a perk you really want, of course.
And you displace all of these perk re-rolls.
All of them.
And then you go through them all.
And if you don't like what you see, you re-roll once.
I mean, it's only gonna be once, I guess.
But it's better than nothing, right?
But you get it cheap.
Because the other one you re-roll...
There's still gonna be a 200, all of them.
Except, so when you re- yeah.
I think you know what I mean.
What do we got?
I...
I may just take greed.
And also, this is another test.
The extra perk does not work backwards.
It does say, from now on.
But maybe that could be interpreted as, from now on, in the holy mountains, you haven't picked a perk yet.
You know what I mean?
Good to know that doesn't mean that.
I'm gonna get greed.
Okay!
Okay.
Very dope.
I may actually just go back down.
There's not much to do up here.
I could try and go kill...
the alchemist.
Hmm...
Do I have the skills for that?
It's a bit greedy.
Let's uh, let's wait with that.
Just a bit longer.
I wanna have a little bit more HP first.
It's kind of important.
And look at this one!
This is- They'll set at 800.
Oh, that's so weird.
So they're only linked to all of them.
I mean, they're always linked.
But it's like you disconnect one from the network once.
In a way.
If that makes sense.
I gotta try, uh...
what I just said in practice.
I need to see exactly how that would work.
What is it with these eldritch portals?
I've seen so many in this run.
At least it seems like the SEMA doesn't burn.
Maybe because it's a light alcoholic drink?
Oh, never mind, it does burn.
But not very aggressively.
It's not like whiskey that just burns away.
And we are actually quite powerful at this point.
Being here with this amount of damage is... pretty dope.
And look, when I go in here, this counts as water!
SEMA counts as just wet.
You don't get flammable or anything like that.
You are wet.
I actually gotta go take a painkiller real quick.
I still have pains in my tooth.
Or like in my gums.
But that's normal.
It's supposed to be up to 14 days.
I'm gonna quickly be right back.